<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Jaggy Gauran</title>
        <link>https://jag.gy</link>
        <description>I write about design, development, and any other thing that comes to mind.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 03:51:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/webmasterish/vuepress-plugin-feed</generator>
        <atom:link href="https://jag.gy/feed.atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TIL Javascript and Picture-in-Picture]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/til-javascript-and-picture-in-picture/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/til-javascript-and-picture-in-picture/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 18:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a lot of sites, you can right click (sometimes twice) to see the &quot;Enter in Picture in Picture&quot; option. There are some sites like Netflix or Twtich does some DOM magic to prevent that.
Here's two javascript snippets I paste on the dev console so I can watch while working.
The safari one's the thing I just learned today!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Working as Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/working-as-adults/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/working-as-adults/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 03:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last Friday, Sean started briefed me on a feature that we want to build in to a new product we're working on. Before even any development, or prototyping happened, I had a list of questions that are focused on the flow of the feature, who the users of the feature will be, and things realted to that aspect.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Switching Layouts in Nuxt]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/switching-layouts-in-nuxt/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/switching-layouts-in-nuxt/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In Nuxt you can switch layouts in your pages by adding a layout: 'layout-name' property in your page attributes. With projects that have consistent design, only using layouts for well, layouts, this is fine but there can be caveats to this.
Let's say when you log in, the user is redirected to a dashboard with a completely different design, Nuxt keeps the CSS of the default.vue layout and the CSS of the components used in the layout.
Here are two things I've seen people use to work around the issue.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designing Type CMS]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/designing-type-cms/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/designing-type-cms/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 06:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Now that we've started to yet again write another CMS, how do we go about it? In my case, whenever I write any product or package, I tend to start designing the ideal design and start adding in compromises depending on external factors (mostly my own technical knowhow).
So, let's just jump into it and let's build this!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artboards, Artboards, Artboards]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/artboards-artboards-arboards/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/artboards-artboards-arboards/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a CMS... and failing]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/building-a-cms-and-failing/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/building-a-cms-and-failing/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here’s a stupid story of me trying to build yet another CMS, why I’m building it, and what I have so far.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Writing More]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/writing-more/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/writing-more/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 03:34:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[My friend Martin just sent me two links a couple of minutes ago:

2020.destroytoday.com
Frank Chimero Redesign Blog: The Popeye Moment

I want to do the same thing. It's not like anybody really keeps track of my writing, but like the fact that I can keep a public archive of the things I'm working on.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why I use full names when designing forms]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/why-i-use-full-names-when-desiging-forms/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/why-i-use-full-names-when-desiging-forms/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 07:23:39 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Whenever I sign up on services online, it always stands out whenever there are separate fields for the first and last name. With the projects I work on, I always use a single field for the name. When clients ask to split the name into multiple fields, it ends up in a pretty long discussion why I think it's unnecessary.]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://jag.gy/../assets/dist/03/full-name.jpg">
            </enclosure>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building my site with Vuepress]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/building-my-site-with-vuepress/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/building-my-site-with-vuepress/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 04:50:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[
Wow. I rework my site more than I write entries.

I usually go for a CMS but markdown-it, the markdown parser Vuepress uses, has an extensive plugin gallery that solves a lot of what I need.
Turns out, Vuepress is not just for building docs anymore!
Here’s how I wrote the theme, plugins I am using, and the two ways I deploy my site, and the gotchas along the way.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Some Unique Title]]></title>
            <link>https://jag.gy/some-unique-slug/</link>
            <guid>https://jag.gy/some-unique-slug/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 05:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>